etenders.in 2018-12-20

# eTendering

We have created this Privacy Policy to explain what personal information we collect about you and the purposes for which we may use such personal information. By submitting personal information to us you consent to our collection and use of it as set out in this Privacy Policy.

Nextenders (India) Private Limited is a company registered in India whose registered office is at Yuchit, Juhu Tara Road, Mumbai—400 049, Maharashtra. The company specializes in providing eTendering, ePerocurement and eAuction solutions with the objective of streamlining the government and enterprise procurement process.

The Service Provider has a strong commitment to your privacy and the confidentiality of the information we collect. The Service Provider provides this Privacy and Confidentiality Policy ("Policy") for the benefit of all of its visitors and Merchants. If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Service Provider's information practices, or this Policy, please contact the Service Provider at support.eauction@nextenders.com.

This Policy and the Usage Agreement (Term of Use) govern your use of the Portal and participation in the Portal, and, together, constitute the "Terms and Conditions.” By clicking on the " **ACCEPT** " button below, or signing a hard copy of the form and returning it to the Service Provider/faxing it to the number indicated, the Merchant accepts and is legally bound by the Terms and Conditions.

 _Notice to Non-Indian Merchant_

. Please note that the information you enter on the Service Provider’s website ("the Portal"), or otherwise provide to the Service Provider, may be transferred outside of your country, for the purposes of processing, by the Service Provider or its subsidiaries or affiliates located in India or elsewhere, in order to provide you with the services of this website and the website. By agreeing to this Policy, you consent to the transfer of all such information to India or any other country decided by the Service Provider and the processing of that information by the Service Provider in the manner described in this Policy.

 _Contact Information_

. When you sign-up to participate on the website, the Service Provider will ask you for certain information that identifies you and allows the Service Provider to contact you ("Contact Information"). The Service Provider collects Contact Information to provide the requested products and services. The Service Provider may also use Contact Information to contact you regarding the new Service Provider product offerings. You may choose to limit or refuse these types of communications.

Occasionally, the Service Provider may provide your Contact Information to its Business Partners whose products or services might be of interest to you. The Service Provider will provide you the opportunity to limit or deny third party access to your Contact Information. The Service Provider may name your Organisation as a user in advertising, promotional, and marketing materials.

The Service Provider may disclose aggregate information about our Merchants with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. This data is used to customize the content and advertising of our Portal, and to provide the best customer experience possible. Aggregate information will not reveal the identity of any individual or the organisation.

The Service Provider has implemented technical, environmental, and administrative measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of all information under its control.

While the Service Provider links to websites that share its respect for privacy, the Service Provider is not responsible for the information practices or the content of such web sites.

 _Transactional Data_

. The Service Provider will collect data from your interaction with the website and your use of the Service Provider's products and services ("Transactional Data"). The Service Provider will maintain such Transactional Data in strict confidence and with complete security. The Service Provider may make limited use of Transactional Data, consistent with the Usage Agreement. The Service Provider will not disclose organisation-specific Transactional Data. Transactional Data will only be disclosed in aggregate form, without any information that would directly or indirectly reveal the identity of an individual firm. The Service Provider will disclose only historical Transactional Data. Any such disclosure will not threaten to reveal competitively sensitive information or provide the opportunity for anti-competitive behaviour.
